

# **Jhonny Robert Sousa Santos**

**Quality Assurance Software Engineer** 

#### Contact

### Phone

+5598992202158

#### E-mail

jhonnyrobert.s@outlook.com

#### Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jhonny-robert/

#### **Address**

Neiva Moreira Ave. 400, Canário, 208 - Calhau. São Luís, MA. 65071-383

### GitHub

https://github.com/jhonnyrobert

# **Soft Skills**

- Communication
- Creativity
- Problem solving
- Adaptability
- Resilience
- Proactivity
- Critical and analytical view

# **Hobbies**

- Cooking
- Muay Thai
- Jiu Jitsu
- Action Figure Painting
- Board and Virtual Games
- Manga and Anime

### **About Me**

Since 2014, I work actively in the Information Technology as a Systems Analyst and Quality Analyst.

I have knowledge in business process modeling, requirements gathering, and software review, analysis and testing.

Ultimately, I have expertise in product documentation, negotiation, customer service, business rules, project management, among others.

#### **Education**

# Masters in Software Engineering

State University of Maranhão - UEMA

# **Majors in Information Systems**

University of Dom Bosco - UNDB

# **Hard Skills**

- Software Testing Automation
- Project Management
- Software Engineering
- CI / CD
- UI / UX
- Postman
- Jmeter
- CYpress
- Cavy
- AppiumRobotFramework
- Git
- BDD

# **Patterns & Methodologies**

- Scrum
- Desing Thinking
- MVC / MVVM
- Jira

# **Programming Languages**

- JavaScript
- Ruby
- Python
- Java

### Career

### **Quality Assurance**

Gazin Tech 2022

- Tested and refined software and released it into production;
- · Developed test scripts;
- · Business rules verification.

# **Quality Assurance**

FWK - Innovation Design. 2021 -

- Developed and implemented software solutions aligned with client requests;
- Tested and refined software and released it into production;
- Developed test scripts;
- Business rules verification.

### COO

ImaginaKIDS. 2020 - 2021

Management of product Roadmap aligned with client requests

#### Teacher

Lesson - School of Technology and Innovation 2019 - 2021

Teaching of Computational Thinking, Robotics and Design Thinking.

# **Software Homologation**

Dom Bosco University - UNDB 2018 - 2019

I worked on development, testing and homologation of internal applications, mainly within TOTVS ERP.

# FrontEnd Development

Prisma Software Studio 2018 - 2019

FrontEnd web development with Laravel Framework.

### Science Researcher

Foundation for Support in Science Research and Technological Development of Maranhão - FAPEMA 2014 - 2018

I worked on the development of a serious game aimed at teaching children with autism and deficit of attention